Where the heck am I?
A lake?
What am I doing here?
I was just…
That's right!
Oh no!
If I don't do something, that
vending machine's in trouble!
I was sure I'd die from a fall like that.
But I guess I survived.
Well, first things first.
Wait, huh?
What's going on?
Why can't I move?
Someone help me, please! Hello there! Huh?
Did I hear my own voice just now?
Okay, calm down
Thank you very much!
Yup, that's my voice!
I look forward to serving you
again I recognize this spiel.
I've heard those words countless times.
You could even win a reward.
I'm a huge fan of any
and all vending machines.
Everyone knows they're my passion.
I'd never mistake that sound.
Which means...
For some reason, I've been
turned into a vending machine!
So i died and have been
reborn as a vending
machine huh as if that could happen no
matter how obsessed i was there's no way
i could turn into one whoa this is awesome
there's no other way to explain it i am
a vending machine i'm fully stocked with
reasonably priced goods and my new
rectangular body is the perfect combination of
elegance and functionality hold on a sec
this can't be happening becoming a vending
machine is the worst or is it being reborn
as the thing i loved could this be some
sort of gift from the divine well there's
no changing what i am now not sure what
it says about me or my fandom that i've
just accepted this hello there thank you.
very much.
I look forward to serving you again.
You could even win a reward.
Too bad. You win!
Please insert coins.
Are those phrases all I can say?
I wonder what else I can do.
You're a vending machine.
Focus. Become it.
Surely you can operate yourself.
This is your body.
Understand it.
Oh, in my brain!
Wait, I don't have a brain.
A bunch of text and numbers
popped up in my mind.
Are these the goods I have for sale?
There are only two types.
You can use your points to
change your current inventory.
Huh? Really?
So I can change what I'm
selling? Points, huh?
That must be what PT stands for.
The money you earn is
converted into points.
You may spend points to replenish or
make changes to your stocked goods,
as well as acquire new functions.
That makes sense.
I did some investigating on my own.
It seems spending points not only
lets me keep items hot or cold,
it also lets me do things
like heat up frozen food?
and even add hot water
to cup ramen on demand.
I might as well test
out my other functions
and check out what kind
of items I can sell.
Oh, it looks like I have everything I could
buy from the vending machines back home.
Let's try spending 10 points to switch
one of my items to cold milk tea.
It worked.
Talk about convenient.
100 yen is a good price.
It says here.
I can turn 100 yen into one point.
All right.
Time to see what else I can do.
After experimenting a little bit more.
I realized one important thing.
My new body doesn't run on electricity.
Instead it seems I consume
points to keep myself powered on.
I use one point an hour.
So I need 24 points a day to function.
Which means I have to sell at least
2400 yen worth of product every day.
I still have nearly a thousand points.
So I can run for about a month.
But I shouldn't waste any points
until I can get a steady income.
Wait.
Will I actually get
any customers out here?
Nobody's come by!
All I'm doing is losing points here!
If this keeps up, I won't make
enough and I'll run out of juice!
Huh?
A frog?
But it's almost as big as a person.
Plus, it's wearing armor
and holding a weapon.
You know, I should probably
be a little more surprised,
but turning into a vending machine
kind of one ups this oh hello there
uh um hi there
hold on stop
three damage durability
has been decreased by
three what's durability
if your durability is
exhausted the vending
machine will break and become
unusable so it's like hit
points in a video Okay,
how many do I have left?
There it is.
These must be my stats.
Everything but durability
and toughness is zero.
I suppose a vending machine
doesn't need those stats.
Wait, magic?
Does magic exist in this world?
You can spend points in order
to restore your durability.
That's good.
I still have about 900 points left.
Maybe I can get through this.
Oh crap, this is really bad.
I don't want to get hit by that!
There has to be some sort of
self-defense function in here somewhere.
Let's see.
Pour hot water, transaction
fanfare, big winner roulette.
I can't use any of these!
Come on, there's got to be something
I can do to get out of this!
Two damage.
Durability has been decreased by two.
Aw, damn it!
I need help each other!
Durability has been decreased by four.
Blessing? What's this?
It's a special power granted by a god.
You may acquire a
blessing without spending
any of your points I
don't really understand,
but it's some sort of magic, right?
Okay, let's do it Can I even use
swordsmanship or martial arts?
Last time I checked I don't
have any arms or legs.
There has to be something else
Barrier deploys an invisible
barrier around you.
You can designate what
objects are allowed through.
Yeah, I picked that one
You could even win a reward!
Yeah!
Behold the invincible vending machine!
I look forward to serving you again.
Huh?
Wait a second.
How come I'm losing so
many points so quickly?
Huh?
Give it up, guys!
All you're doing is wasting
your time and my points!
Whew!
I made it!
I might as well get my
durability back now.
There. Good as new.
I've got 311 points left.
I can still last over 10 days.
But unless somebody buys something, my
points will dry up and I'll run out of power.
But what happens after that?
Will I die?
What a tragically short life.
Or, I suppose, a short operating
time? Somebody! Anybody!
Please help me!
It would have been pretty cool to
sell at least one thing before dying.
There's no use trying to hide from me!
What the?
I could have sworn they were around here
Thank goodness, I'm starving.
I'm so hungry I can't
muster up any strength!
Why does this kind of
thing always happen to me?
I even dropped my bag
with all my food in it!
It's my fault!
I should have listened!
My parents were right, I'm
not cut out to be a hunter!
What's she talking about?
I have to defeat frog
fiends for their meat.
For some reason,
my attacks don't hit when I'm by
myself and I just want to take a nap!
Things will be better if
I at least add some food.
Wait, what's that?
So weird.
Looks like some kind of stone
monument, but too Middle.
The shape is really peculiar, too.
And are those drinks behind the glass?
There's a bunch of writing,
but I can't read it.
Hello, man!
Wait, what was that voice?
Where'd it come from?
Please insert coins. The box.
How is it talking?
Also, coins? It wants money?
Would a copper coin work?
Maybe it has to be at least silver.
What if it needs gold?
As if I even had that on me.
It said something about
inserting the coins.
I guess it can't hurt to put in
a copper and see what happens.
Looks like a copper coin
wasn't enough after all.
That is an unsupported currency.
If you acquire the coin conversion
function, you can accept it.
What?
For real?
Hold on just one second.
Oh, there it is.
I can swing 100 points.
I didn't increase the prices, but
the numbers went up all the same.
Huh?
Why did the number change?
A thousand owa?
Aw, but that's a whole silver coin.
So this world's unit of
currency is called an owa.
It's expensive, but I
need food for my belly.
I'm about to beg!
It lit up.
Ooh, does it want me to push something?
Hmm...
Wow, there's a picture of soup on here!
Huh? What was that?
Something came out!
It's not gonna chomp down if
I reach my hand in, right?
I wouldn't do that!
So hurry up and take it!
I highly recommend this
brand of corn soup!
Oh, it's so warm!
Uh, do I twist the top to open it?
Oh!
It smells good!
Wow, what is this?
It's so tasty!
I wouldn't want Mrs.
to hear this, but it's way better
than the food I had in town!
Why do I feel so happy?
Helping someone out gives me a sense
of satisfaction I haven't felt before.
Aw, man, I drank everything already.
I bet the other stuff
in there is tasty, too.
The clear-looking ones are probably water,
And I already know what that tastes like,
so I'll try out the
light brown drink next.
It seems she took a liking
to the milk tea as well.
Afterwards, she bought three more corn
soups, along with a bottle of water.
I earned six silver coins and 30
coppers for a total of 6,300 owa,
which means I got back 63 points!
A full stomach must have broken
the tension she was holding.
As soon as she finished
eating, she fell asleep.
She's a bit of an odd one,
but she's my best customer.
Don't worry.
I'll keep you safe with my barrier.
The trash cleans itself up!
I've got to be the most advanced
vending machine in this other world!
Looks like I fell asleep.
Well, it's a good thing
no monsters showed up.
I ended up spending a whole bunch.
But I'm feeling a lot better now.
And it's all thanks to you.
Thank you very much.
Uh, yes.
Um, thank you.
That's right.
I forgot that you can talk.
Or maybe...
Are you only able to say certain phrases?
I actually know someone who's inventing
tools that have magical power inside them.
I wonder if you're something similar.
If you can understand what I'm saying,
then I'd like it if you said something.
Anything.
Hello there.
Yes, I knew it.
I bet Hulemy would be
interested in meeting you.
Oh, I haven't told you my name yet.
You can call me Lamas.
Lamas, huh?
Has a nice ring to it.
I got it.
How's this sound?
Whenever you want to say yes,
you can just say hello there,
and we'll use a different
phrase to mean no.
Too bad.
Okay, is that what you
want to use for know then?
Hello there. Yes, huh? Perfect.
Let's see.
Can you tell me your name?
Too bad.
That's okay.
So what are you doing out here all alone?
Are you on some sort of
important quest? Too bad.
I hope I'm not being too forward.
Are you lonely by yourself? Hello there.
I thought that was the case.
For some reason you looked lonely.
Would it be okay with you if
I moved you somewhere else?
Hello there!
That's awesome!
I was thinking about bringing you
back and showing you to Hewla me.
I bet the two of you would
hit it off right away.
Hello there!
You're cool with it? Great!
Give me just a second.
Up we go!
Are you for real?
I have to weigh at least 500 kilograms!
Whoa, you're heavier than you look.
Thank you for saving me!
Apparently, Lamas has a blessing
called the blessing of might.
I suppose that explains why
she's so incredibly strong.
I'm just going to take a short break here.
I'm starting to get hungry.
I wonder if I can buy more
of that tasty yellow soup.
The thing is, corn soup
isn't all that filling.
Oh, what else could I stock?
Oh, how about that?
Huh?
That surprised me.
You are glowing.
Did you change your items?
What is that?
Could it be food?
Hello there!
I thought it might be!
It's the same price.
Maybe I'll buy some.
Oh, what a weird texture!
The only thing I can really taste is
salt, but I can't stop eating them!
Oh, no, no, no! No,
I'm gonna burn through the
rest of my money at this rate,
but I can't control myself!
Thanks to that, I'm back up to 320 points!
Next, I want to try to adjust
the price of mineral water.
It'd be great if I could offer it for
less, but my life kind of depends on it.
We should reach the entrance of this
stratum soon stratum after that.
We'll take a break in a nearby village
Wait Lamas, you're all right.
Karios and Gorth boy am I
glad to see you guys whoo!
We were worried after your
group came back all but dead.
Thank goodness.
You're okay.
Sorry about that By the
way, what's this thing?
It's a magic tool with its own consciousness
that I found near the lakeside.
Whenever you put money in,
it gives you a tasty item.
Really?
I've never heard of magic tools being
discovered in the Clear
Flow Lake stratum before.
Should I have not brought it out?
It's not a problem.
You know how things are in the dungeon.
Whatever you find lying around
in a stratum is yours to keep.
Dungeon?
I don't really understand
what they're talking about.
They make it sound like we're in some
kind of labyrinth, but there's a sky.
Hey, do you think we could
try out your magic item?
Sure, let me ask it.
Do you mind? Hello?
Whoa, it talked!
Right, you said it had a consciousness.
This'd fetch a high price.
He's not for sale.
I'm going to bring him back with me
so Hulemy can take a look at him.
That engineer who's a magic item fanatic.
A silver coin, huh?
Pretty pricey.
But I'll have one of these.
Please insert coins.
Well, I'll be.
This stuff's delicious.
So's this one.
I wonder what this
fried-looking thing tastes like.
Let me try.
In the end, they bought at
least one of every item I had.
Being able to drink both hot and
cold things on demand is great.
We aren't allowed to leave our posts.
So could you bring it by now and again?
Sure.
And with that, I tripled my customer base.
Wait a sec.
I've had enough of your crying.
You're wasting our time here.
You're just making things
worse for yourself.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
I should ask you the same,
because it looks like a bunch of nasty
-looking thugs are ganging
up on a helpless girl.
Bet you think you're some
kind of hero, don't you?
This will teach you to butt in.
You got no one but
yourself to blame, Missy!
We'll let you off easy,
but next time you're done.
I look forward to serving you again.
Not again.
None of my hits landed.
They didn't hurt you, did they?
Are you all right? Yes.
All thanks to you.
Oh, missus! I'm home!
Lamas, you made it back.
I was so worried for you.
I'm sorry, missus.
Oh, Miss, I missed you!
You're alive?
I'm not dreaming, am I?
You're not.
It's really me, Munami.
Oh, I was afraid I'd never see you again.
Oh, sorry.
When I asked the returning hunters, they
said they ran off and left you by yourself.
As revenge, I told everyone
around town what they did.
They won't be able to find work again.
Anyway what's that uh ah I found it by the
lake you brought back
another weird artifact
This one's different
he's surprisingly useful
and he helped me out when I was in a bind
So you're going back to the
surface to show it to Hulemy
do you have enough for the
transfer circle uh can I
borrow some money a transfer
circle huh apparently that's
a thing in this world also
llamas's lack of funds is kind
of my fault whoops sorry
about you you'll just have to
work at our end to earn your
fare how about this why don't
we keep the box you found
outside it can sell its wares
and attract customers hello
there it really can speak
Good.
It'll drum up business.
And so, I found myself a new
home right in front of the inn.
There's a sky,
but I soon learned that this was actually
a dungeon stratum called Clear Flow Lake.
I quickly gained popularity since my goods
were unlike anything they had seen before.
Then, when night fell, Llamas would carry
me over to a safe place near the gate.
I'm feeling kind of thirsty, but
I'm getting tired of this election.
Well, that's because you're buying
at least five of them every night!
I suppose I could switch up my stock.
What's my current status?
After all the business
I've been getting recently,
looks like I've saved up
over 3,000 points Great!
What should I add?
One should always keep the customer's needs
in mind first I've got just the thing!
All the items are different!
Whoa, this one costs three silver coins.
But at that price, it has to be good.
I gotta try it.
How hot?
How do you open this thing?
Look, are those pictures?
Those must be instructions.
This item became famous in a
certain electric town back home.
So the manufacturer added meticulous
instructions so even tourists could enjoy it.
Oh, it worked.
Sure smells good.
What?
This is amazing.
It might be my new favorite.
What ingredients did they use in this?
The flavor in it is so
complex, yet incredibly light.
Damn, I want alcohol now.
Scooch over a bit. Hold on.
I was going to buy something else.
They're totally hooked.
Hurry up, then.
I got plenty more where that came from.
My goods only got more popular.
Words soon got around
about the canned Odin?
Which caused a bit of an
uproar in the village!
I think the weather getting colder
lately might have helped sales too.
What's more, the sports drink I
added to my stock was also selling.
I don't sell canned Odin during the day.
That's when the restaurant
does most of its business.
And I don't want to step on any toes.
Instead, I help attract guests.
Isn't this the girl Llamas saved
in the alley the other day?
Excuse me! Hello there!
I wanted to talk first so I'd have
the advantage in negotiations!
Stop that!
What was that about?
When the sun starts to set, Llamas
carries me over to the gate.
She said moving me around
like before was inconvenient,
so she bought a wooden frame
that she could put on her back.
I'm about to burst.
I'll be heading back now.
A guest came by the inn today and
told me tons of interesting stories.
Hello there.
How are things on your side?
You could even win a reward.
Did you have fun today?
I hope someday you and I can
have a real conversation.
That's one of the reasons I want to hurry
and save up so we can go see Hulemy.
Thank you very much.
You don't have to thank me.
Don't forget it.
You were the one who saved me, Boxo.
Boxo?
It feels kind of weird
to keep calling you you.
What do you think? You win!
Glad you like it.
Here's to the future, Boxo.
Waking up as a vending machine in
another world is as ridiculous as can be.
But for some reason,
I'm starting to think this wouldn't
be such a bad life after all.
Thank you very much!
I look forward to serving you again!